gwcu.org 2012-10-15

# Privacy Policy - Terms, Conditions, and Disclosures - Goldenwest Credit Union

Goldenwest Credit Union is committed to providing you with financial products and services to meet your financial goals. We are equally committed to protecting your privacy.

Therefore, we have developed a privacy policy. This privacy notice describes our policies and practices that protect your privacy. If you have any questions after reading it, please contact us at (801) 621-4550 or 1-800-283-4550.

### Information We Collect About You

We collect information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications and other forms; such as your current or past employers, and information from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions;
  * Records of your transactions with us, our affiliates, or those companies that work with us to provide you with diverse financial products and services;
  * Information obtained through consumer reporting agency;
  * We may obtain information you provide online when you visit our web site. This includes information you provide us in online applications; Account Access transactions, or information you send to us by e-mail.

We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, as permitted by law.

### Parties Who Receive Information From Us

We may disclose your name and address to third parties who perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. To protect our members' privacy we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide. We do not permit these companies to sell the member information to other third parties.

In order to conduct the business of the credit union, we may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you under other circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, conduct the operations of our credit union, follow your instructions as you authorize, or protect the security of our financial records.

If you terminate your membership at Goldenwest Credit Union, we will not share information we have collected about you, except as may be permitted or required by law.

### Internet Privacy

Goldenwest Credit Union uses Verisign's digital certificate key to secure account information sent between our server and your browser. Whenever you use Account Access, Goldenwest's server will respond to your transmission by sending this key that is authenticated by your browser. This communication key encrypts the data sent by you and Goldenwest Credit Union decrypts it when we receive it. Goldenwest uses firewalls that are designed to protect your accounts from unauthorized access from outside the credit union.

You are responsible for protecting the secrecy of your password. We recommend you not store secure pages in your cache or leave your computer unattended while you are logged into Account Access.

To give you the the best online experience, our Internet home banking system utilizes "cookies," which are very small files that a web site sends to the member's browser for record-keeping purposes. Cookies function as identification cards, recording passwords and preferences. Cookies cannot be executed as code, nor can they deliver viruses. Browsers can be set to deliver a message when a cookie has been sent, allowing the member to decide whether to accept or reject it. In order to tailor web site content to our members' interests, all cookies must be accepted. All of our cookies are temporary, which means that they are active only as long as the member's browser is running. Cookies expire when the session has ended.

### How We Protect Your Information

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.

### What Can You Do To Help Protect Your Privacy?

  * Keep your information with us current. It is important that we have current information on how to reach you. If we detect potentially fraudulent or unauthorized use of an account, we will attempt to contact you immediately. If your address or phone number changes, please let us know.
  * Protect your account numbers, card numbers and PINs (personal identification numbers) and passwords. Never keep your PIN with your debit or credit card.
  * Use caution when disclosing your account numbers, social security numbers, etc.
  * Goldenwest Credit Union staff will never call you and ask for your account number.

### Important Reasons To Feel Secure At Goldenwest

  * Over 71 years of credit union experience.
  * Well-trained employees who are committed to keeping your personal information secure.
  * At no time will we discuss private information outside the credit union except as necessary in the course of business.
  * Up-to-date technology including the latest data-encryption software.
  * Physical safeguards and quality controls help ensure the security and confidentiality of our members' personal financial information.
